I spent 11 years in the U.S. Navy as a fighter pilot.
For 18 years I flew fighters for the United States Navy.
I spent 20 years working in the U.S. intelligence community.
I served as the fourth director of national intelligence.
I spent 25 years as a senior official with the CIA.
I retired from the Navy as a one-star admiral after 32 years of service.
I worked on highly classified UAP programs for the government as a senior scientist.
I spent 32 years in and out of government in national security.
I worked 28 years as an astrophysicist on highly classified UAP programs
for the United States government and for the defense industry.
I'm a professor in the Department of Pathology at Stanford University School of Medicine.
And for the last 10 years or so, I've been working with the Department of Defense
and people in the CIA on the UAP topic.
I've come to the conclusion that we are not only not alone in the universe,
but we have been discovered by an intelligence from some other part of the universe.
There's evidence we are not alone.
Humanity is not the only intelligent species in the universe.
We're not alone in the universe.
It wouldn't be so arrogant to suggest there are no other forms of life out there.
Humanity is not the only intelligence in the universe.
UAPs are real, they're here, and they're not human.
There are other intelligences that have highly advanced craft interacting with the human population.
They are here, this is real, it's happening, it's happening now.
Non-human intelligence exists, it's been interacting with humanity,
and it's been doing so on this planet for a long time.
We are not the only intelligent life form in the universe.
There's something here on the planet with us that is intelligent and more intelligent than us.
This is the biggest discovery in human history.
My name is Lou Elizondo.
In 2009, my life changed forever.
That's when I was recruited into a highly sensitive government program
that investigated unidentified aerial phenomenon, UAP, also commonly known as UFOs.
My work for the U.S. government goes back almost 30 years to when I joined the U.S. Army.
From there, I had the good fortune of being recruited into various programs within military intelligence.